(Leonard:)You left with his date.
(Leonard:)Friends don't do that to each other.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Oh.
All right, noted.
(Sheldon(on phone):)- Sorry.
- "Sorry"? That's all you can say is "sorry"?
(Leonard:)Take it, Raj.
It's more than I've ever gotten.
(Sheldon:)And may I point out...
(Sheldon:)...she wouldn't have asked me to go
if you weren't drunk and boring.
(Dr Koothrappali:)- Drunk?
- And boring. Her words.
(Dr Koothrappali:)I knew it, he moves to America
and becomes an alcoholic.
(Raj:)I'm not an alcoholic.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Then why were you drunk?
(Raj:)It was just this one time, Papa, I swear.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Are you in denial? Do we have
to come over and do an intervention?
(Mrs Koothrappali:)Don't embarrass him
in front of his friends.
All right. Carry us outside.
(Dr Koothrappali:)We want to talk to you in private.
- But, Papa, please...
- Now, Rajesh.
(Raj(to Leonard and Sheldon):)I have to go.
DR. KOOTHRAPPALI: Now, listen to me...
- At least wait till I get into the hall.
[DOOR CLOSES]
(Sheldon:)Okay, well, good night.